<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <array name="dashboard_items">
        <item>My Course Schedule\nالجدول الدراسي</item>
        <item>My Marks\nالدرجات</item>
        <item>My Study Plan\nالخطة الدراسية</item>
        <item>MY Course Advice\nالارشاد الاكاديمي</item>
        <item>Letter Request\nطلب رسالة</item>
        <item>My Finance\nالحسابات</item>
        <item>My Profile\nملف الطالب</item>
        <item>My Inbox\nصندوق الوارد</item>
        <item>Google ClassRoom\nغرف جوجل الصفية</item>
        <item>Library\nالمكتبة</item>
        <item>Grade Conversion\nتحويل الدرجات</item>
        <item>Add/Drop\nإضافة قطرة</item>
    </array>

    <array name="faq_question">
        <item>Who can register for different programs?</item>
        <item>Does Al Dar offer scholarships?</item>
        <item>Does Al Dar accept transfer students?</item>
        <item>Does Al Dar accept visiting students?</item>
        <item>Can I visit the college before admission?</item>
        <item>Does Al Dar provide residence visa to the students?</item>
        <item>Accordion ContentDoes Al Dar provide transport to the students?</item>
        <item>Am I eligible for admission even if I do not have IELTS or TOEFL?</item>
        <item>What if I want to change my registration?</item>
        <item>What is a pre-requisite course?</item>
        <item>How many courses do I need to register?</item>
        <item>What are the possibilities of career opportunities available on completion of studies at Al Dar?</item>
        <item>Can I pay my fees in installments?</item>
        <item>Is there any platform where student(s) can raise their concerns/complaints?</item>
    </array>


    <array name="faq_answer">
        <item>All students who fulfill the minimum admission criteria of Al Dar are eligible for the
            admission and the registration for various programs available at Al Dar University
            College.
        </item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar offers a wide range of scholarships and discounts intended to support
            students in continuing their education. There are many types of scholarships/ grants
            (High School, sibling, government employee, international student, financial aid)
            available to the students.
        </item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar accepts transfer students as per the transfer policy of the Al
            DarUniversity College.
        </item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar accepts visiting students based on the permission granted by their
            university.
        </item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar gladly welcomes all the prospective students and their parents/relatives
            to visit the campus and have a campus tour of all the facilities provided to the
            students. They are also welcome to have interaction with faculties and the staff if they
            wish so.
        </item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar provides residence visa to all the admitted students based on the approval
            of visa request by the UAE Immigration Authority.
        </item>
        <item>Accordion ContentDoes Al Dar provide transport to the students?\nYes, Al Dar provides transportation
            to the students (morning and evening)for Ajman, Sharjah and Dubai.</item>
        <item>Yes, you are eligible for the admission but in that case you will be given provisional/conditional
            admission and will be limited to 15 credit hours of General Education courses along with Intensive English Program in order to enhance level of your English.</item>

        <item>You can change your registration during the drop/add period as per scheduled in the academic calendar.</item>

        <item>A pre-requisite course means a course, which a student must pass before enrolling in the advanced course.</item>

        <item>The study/course load is the total number of credit hours that student allowed to register during one
            semester. The maximum registration is 18 credit hours, and the minimum registration is 12 credit hours.</item>

        <item>At Al Dar there is a career office which works very closely with the alumni and the corporate sector
            in order to explore suitable employment opportunities for the students as per their specialization.</item>

        <item>Al Dar offers flexible mode of payment in order to facilitate the students in their payment of the fees.</item>

        <item>Yes, Al Dar has the policy to Hear from Students. In case, if student(s) have any concerns/complaints
            they can drop an email at complaints@aldar.ac.ae</item>
    </array>

    <array name="books">
        <item>Title</item>
        <item>Author</item>
        <item>Call Number</item>
        <item>Publisher</item>
    </array>
</resources>