<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <array name="dashboard_items">
        <item>My Course Schedule\nجدول دراستي</item>
        <item>My Marks\nعلاماتي</item>
        <item>My Study Plan\nخطة دراستي</item>
        <item>MY Course Advice\nنصيحة بالطبع بلدي</item>
        <item>Letter Request\nطلب رسالة</item>
        <item>My Finance\nأموالي</item>
        <item>My Profile\nملفي</item>
        <item>My Inbox\nصندوق الوارد</item>
        <item>Google ClassRoom\nجوجل الفصول الدراسية</item>
        <item>Library\nمكتبة</item>
    </array>

    <array name="faq_question">
        <item>Who can register for different programs?</item>
        <item>Does Al Dar offer scholarships?</item>
        <item>Does Al Dar accept transfer students?</item>
        <item>Does Al Dar accept visiting students?</item>
        <item>Can I visit the college before admission?</item>
        <item>Does Al Dar provide residence visa to the students?</item>
    </array>

    <array name="faq_answer">
        <item>All students who fulfill the minimum admission criteria of Al Dar are eligible for the admission and the registration for various programs available at Al Dar University College.</item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar offers a wide range of scholarships and discounts intended to support students in continuing their education. There are many types of scholarships/ grants (High School, sibling, government employee, international student, financial aid) available to the students.</item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar accepts transfer students as per the transfer policy of the Al DarUniversity College.</item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar accepts visiting students based on the permission granted by their university.</item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar gladly welcomes all the prospective students and their parents/relatives to visit the campus and have a campus tour of all the facilities provided to the students. They are also welcome to have interaction with faculties and the staff if they wish so.</item>
        <item>Yes, Al Dar provides residence visa to all the admitted students based on the approval of visa request by the UAE Immigration Authority.</item>
    </array>

    <array name="books">
        <item>Title</item>
        <item>Author</item>
        <item>Call Number</item>
        <item>Publisher</item>
    </array>
</resources>