<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ADUC</string>
    <string name="uni_name">ALDAR University</string>

    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="map_apikey">AIzaSyAepQhzH42X9rObxzFGXMLp6iXsbt2xZlI</string>

    <string name="welcome">Apply for Admission</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to ALDAR University College, We don’t just give students an education and experiences that set them up
        for success in a career.\n\nYour career path begins Here, Take the first step and Apply Now</string>
    <string name="affordable_price">Affordable tuition fees In addition to financial support through scholarship and financial aids</string>
    <string name="flexible_course">ALDAR designs flexible courses offerings that allow students to attend classes during weekdays and weekends</string>
    <string name="accomodation">In ALDAR University College Dubai the Accomodation is availble</string>
    <string name="transport_text">FREE transportation for the student is provided from DUBAI, Sharjah, and, Ajman .</string>
    <string name="tution_text">Affordable tuition fees In addition to financial support through scholarship and financial aids</string>
    <string name="visa_text">ALDAR University College provides Student Visa.</string>
    <string name="support">Expert Support</string>
    <string name="support_text">Aldar University, in-house expert team, is always on hand to help, answer your questions, and guide you in the proper direction.
        \nYou can call, chat, or email us!</string>

    <string name="fee">FEE</string>
    <string name="portal">Portal</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply Now</string>
    <string name="download_boucher">Download Brocher</string>
    <string name="flexible">Flexible course</string>
    <string name="transportation">FREE transportation</string>
    <string name="student_visa">Student visa</string>
    <string name="tution_fee">Affordable tuition fees</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="faq_question">Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_admission">Admission</string>
    <string name="menu_academic">Academics</string>
    <string name="menu_campus">Campus Life</string>
    <string name="menu_research">Research</string>
    <string name="menu_login">Login</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="logout_text">Are you sure to logout ?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="verify">Verify</string>
    <string name="forgot_text">We will send an email and Message, ensure its your personal and correct Username ID</string>
    <string name="verify_text">We have sent you the code on the Phone Number and email you provided, please verify yourself.</string>
    <string name="change_password_text">Please change your password here make sure the password is easy to remember</string>
    <string name="student_id">Student ID</string>
    <string name="studnet_name">Student Name</string>
    <string name="student_course">Programe</string>
    <string name="advisor">Advisor</string>
    <string name="concentration">Concentration</string>
    <string name="my_course_advise">Your Academic Status\nالحالة الاكاديمية</string>
    <string name="your_marks">Here is your marks\n علاماتك</string>
    <string name="instructor_msg">Messages From Instructors</string>
    <string name="compose_write">Compose/Write Mail</string>
    <string name="your_course_schedule">Here is your course schedule\nجدول دراستك</string>
    <string name="financial_statement">Here is your Financial Statement\nالشهادة المالية</string>
    <string name="profile_statement">Here is your profile info\nمعلومات الشخصي</string>
    <string name="letter_request">please add a new request below\nطلب جديد</string>
    <string name="announcement_text">Here is the latest announcement\nأحدث إعلان</string>
    <string name="faq_text">Frequently Asked Questions\nأسئلة مكررة</string>


    <string name="computer_school">School Of Engineering &amp; Technology</string>
    <string name="computer_text">We are proud to offer a wide range of accredited programs in Engineering and Technology that will equip students with the knowledge needed to pursue the career</string>
    <string name="business_school">School Of Business Administration</string>
    <string name="business_text">The School of Business Administration (SBA) at ADUC caters to the need of multicultural workforce in the field of Business and Management.</string>
    <string name="art_school">School Of Arts And Social Sciences</string>
    <string name="art_text">The School of Arts and Social Sciences (SBA) at ADUC caters to the need of multicultural workforce in the field of Business and Management.</string>


    <string name="campus_life">Campus life at ALDAR University College, enjoys the benefits of an urban campus
        as it is located in the heart of the historic business district of Dubai. Movie theaters, shopping centers,
        banks, restaurants, and other facilities are located in the vicinity of the College.\n\n
        The College is situated near the Deira City Centre Metro Station and the GGICO Metro Station. Students commuting from all
        over Dubai have an easy access to the College. Transportation services are provided by the College to major locations in the Northern Emirates.\n\n
        <b>ALDAR University College provides students with the following facilities to enhance their learning experience:</b>\n\n
        Library, fully equipped with books, e-books, journals, magazines, online databases, CDs/DVDs, multimedia rooms, discussion rooms, computers workstations,
        wireless Internet connection, scanning, photocopying, and printing services provides faculty and students a conducive environment for their scholarlyactivities.
        Classrooms and computer laboratories are equipped with smart interactive boards and state-of-the-art workstations.
        Students have access to a spacious lounge to conduct their various extra-curricular activities in a convenient and friendly spot.\n\n
        The College also provides ample parking space with three basement floors.\n</string>


    <string name="ieee_text">
        IEEE is the world’s largest technical professional organization dedicated to advancing technology for the benefits of humanity.
        IEEE and its members inspire a global community to innovate for a better tomorrow through its highly cited publications, conferences,
        technology standards, and professional and educational activities. IEEE is the trusted “voice” for engineering, computing, and technology
        information around the globe.\n\n
        ALDAR IEEE student’s branch was established in 2015 and is led by a committed team of students and faculty from the school of Engineering
        and Technology (SET).\n\n
        Its main purpose is to give students the opportunity to be a part of professional community, get exposed to the technological advancement
        and educational aspects occurring worldwide.\n\n
        <b>Students of the IEEE student branch conduct the following activities:</b>\n\n
        Formulate technical workshops and competitions
        Regulate professional networking through participation in technical events, international conferences and seminars
        Participate in international competitions and enhance the technical knowledge and skills of students in SET
        Coordinate with and organize trips to companies in related fields.
        Encourage IEEE members to connect with local IEEE Sections, share individual benefits and gain volunteering skills\n\n
        To become an IEEE member, you can contact an executive committee member through the following contacts:\n
    </string>

    <string name="about_uae">
        The UAE is a federation of seven Emirates located in the Middle East. The country has emerged as both a dynamic international business centre
        and a laid-back tourist escape. From unspoiled beaches to rugged mountains, and picturesque heritage sites to ultra-modern shopping malls, the
        UAE offers a truly unique lifestyle experience.\n\n
        As the gateway between east and west, the UAE has become a safe and accessible base for leading multinationals from across the globe to establish a
        foothold in the Middle East market, and to explore emerging economies further afield. This expanding business base attracts students and professionals
        from around the world, giving the UAE a unique multicultural identity, where nationals from more than 200 countries live in harmony with the Emirati people.\n\n
         The higher educational landscape in the UAE reflects the cultural mix of the country. With a thirst for innovation, the UAE is also gathering a growing reputation
        for its advancements in research and technological development.\n\n
        One of the fastest growing cities in the world, Dubai is the place where the sophistication of the 21st century meets the unique charm of an ancient trading port.
        With world-class infrastructure and facilities, the city combines the cosmopolitan lifestyle of the western world with eastern traditions and hospitality.\n\n
         Already renowned for its bold ambition, as the home of the world’s tallest building and the world’s largest man-made island, Dubai will continue to grow its
        international stature when it hosts the World Expo in 2020.\n
    </string>

    <string name="about_text">
        ALDAR University College  is a university college of higher learning established in 1994. Since our opening, it has been our endeavor to infuse our
        students with industry-relevant skills and a high level of practical aptitude. This is a challenge and an objective that we continue to pursue to this day.\n\n
        Al Dar draws its student body from several different countries across the region and the world. Therefore, we are extremely proud of the atmosphere
        of diversity that is nourished within our walls and of the eclectic student base visible here every day.\n\n
        We offer a wide portfolio of programs ranging from undergraduate studies to short courses aimed at both students and professionals. Our range of programs
        consists of Bachelor’s Degrees, Associate Degrees, English Language courses and Exam Preparation courses. In line with our plans for growth, our aim is
        to steadily increase our program offerings to cater to the ever-growing demand for quality education. All our programs are industry-related and aim to
        empower our students with the required skills and aptitudes to operate effectively in the modern business environment.\n\n
        As part of our strategy, the university conducts both indoor and outdoor extra-curricular activities to broaden the spectrum of our students’ knowledge
        in order to facilitate personal, professional and academic growth. We fundamentally appreciate that classroom sessions need to be coupled with practical
        training so as to hone student skill sets. With course curriculum modeled on emphasizing core concepts and ultra-modern case studies, we are confident that
        our students are poised to take up the challenges faced in industry today.
    </string>

    <string name="mission_text">
        To offer competitive educational programs in real-world settings and focus on developing and strengthening careers of a diverse population.
        To engage with the society in the creation of knowledge and promotion of research to achieve local and regional development.
    </string>

    <string name="vision_text">
        To be a leading and an internationally recognized higher education institution, contributing to the knowledge society and sustainable development
        of the United Arab Emirates and the Region.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
